https://www.rejoiceinlife.com/admin/privacy-policy.php

Links
...Traditional Nutrition - NLP Coaching and video documentary.
3/22 Tourangeau Cr Varsity Lakes
Gold Coast Qld Australia.
Traditional Nutrition...
Abby Eagle School of Meditation provide
training in Meditation and NLP. They are based on the Gold Coast Qld Australia.
Abby, the owner, is a Stress Management and Personal Development Consultant. He
has a Diploma in Applied Science (Biology), and is a Master Practitioner of NLP,
Ericksonian Hypnosis and Time-Line Therapy. Abby has over 20 years experience
in the personal and spiritual growth fields.
WHO
IS ABBY EAGLE
SCHOOL OF MEDITATION
Abby Eagle School of Meditation is privately owned by Abby Eagle, ABN 48 595 137
583. Contact details at the end of this document.
PERSONAL
INFORMATION
Personal
Information is information or an opinion (including information or an opinion
forming part of a database) whether true or not, and whether recorded in a material
form or not about an individual whose identity is apparent, or can reasonably
be ascertained, from the information or opinion.
It includes all personal information regardless of its source. Personal information
relates to a natural living person. A natural person is a human being rather than,
for example, a company, which may in some circumstances be recognised as a legal
'person' under the law.
The National Privacy Principles (NPPs) apply to the collection of personal information
by an organisation for inclusion in a record or a generally available publication,
but apart from this, the NPPs only apply to personal information an organisation
has collected that it holds in a record.
SENSITIVE
INFORMATION
Sensitive
information is a subset of personal information. It means information or an opinion
about an individual's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership
of political association, religious beliefs or affiliations, philosophical beliefs,
membership of a professional or trade association, membership of a trade union,
sexual preferences or practices, criminal record or health information about an
individual.
Sensitive
information is only collected by Rejoice-In-Life where consent has been obtained,
it is allowed by law, or the collection is necessary for the establishment, exercise
or defence of a legal claim, or for the completion of a service - as in a personal
consultation.
COLLECTION
OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
It
is essential for Abby Eagle School of Meditation to collect personal information
to complete its standard business functions and activities. Information may be
stored in a database on a computer or on hard copy. The purposes for collecting
personal information are:
Provide
efficient communications with our Clientele.
Marketing
and sales promotions so as to inform a Client or prospective Client of products
and services which may be of benefit to them.
Administrative
operations including statistical reports, accounting, record keeping, development
and testing of systems and the training of staff.
Complying
with legislative and regulatory requirements.
We collect personal information only by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably
intrusive way. At or before the time (or, if that is not practicable, as soon
as practicable after) Abby Eagle School of Meditation has collected personal
information from yourself, Abby Eagle School of Meditation will take reasonable
steps to ensure that you are aware of:
Who
we are and how to contact us; and
The
fact that you are able to gain access to information held about you; and
The
purposes for which the information is collected; and
The
organisations (or the types of organisations) to which we usually disclose information
of that kind; and
Any
law that requires the particular information to be collected; and
The
main consequences (if any) for the individual if all or part of the information
is not provided.
Where it is reasonable and practicable to do so, Abby Eagle School of Meditation
will collect personal information directly from yourself. This may occur, for
example, when completing a mailing list form, or request for a product or service
over the telephone. Where it is not reasonable or practical to collect information
from you directly, Abby Eagle School of Meditation may rely upon a third party
however, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you have been made aware
of the matters listed above except to the extent that making you aware of the
matters would pose a serious threat to the life or health of any individual.
In the majority of circumstances
Abby Eagle School of Meditation will require specific consent before we collect,
use or disclose personal information. Consent will usually be obtained in writing,
however there may be some situations where verbal consent is implied and accepted
such as when you continue a telephone conversation with us.
COLLECTION
OF SENSITIVE INFORMATION
Abby Eagle School of Meditation does not collect sensitive information about you
unless you have consented; for example if you were to have a NLP consultation
then it would be implied that you had given consent to collect sensitive information
in the course of assisting you to achieve your desired outcomes.
USE
AND DISCLOSURE
Abby Eagle School of Meditation does not use or disclose personal information about
you to any other party, unless consent is given, (consent may be received directly
from you or may be implied by your conduct.) or it is required to complete a business
transaction, or you would reasonably expect us to do so; or we believe that the
disclosure is necessary to lessen or prevent: a serious and imminent threat to
an individuals life, health or safety; or a serious threat to public health or
public safety; or when it may be required or authorised by law.
Abby Eagle School of Meditation does not lend or sell personal information to
other organisations for marketing purposes, however we may at times provide a
mailing list to a third party organisation to mail correspondence to you or to
a business associate on your behalf.
If
the personal information is to be used for a secondary purpose of direct marketing
then it may not be practical for Abby Eagle School of Meditation to seek your
consent on the first mail out, however in each direct marketing communication
with you, we will draw your attention to the fact that you may express a wish
not to receive any further direct marketing communications from us; and each direct
marketing communication by us to you shall set out our business address and telephone
number; and if the communication is made by fax or email, a fax number or email
address at which we can be contacted.
You have the right at any time to request us not to telephone you or provide you
with further information about our products and services and not to disclose your
information to any other organisations for that purpose.
Please not that personal information collected may be transferred and shared in the event
of the sale of this website / business.
DATA
QUALITY
Abby Eagle School of Meditation will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal
information it collects, uses or discloses is accurate, complete and up to date
in order to effectively conduct its standard business activities. You may contact
us at any time to update your personal information, or to advise that information
held is inaccurate or incomplete.
DATA
SECURITY
Abby Eagle School of Meditation takes all reasonable steps to protect the personal
information it holds about you from misuse and loss, and from unauthorised access,
modification or disclosure. Abby Eagle School of Meditation employs the following
means to ensure that personal information is protected at all times:
Secure premises.
Username
and password required for access to computer systems.
Restricted
access to personal information.
Backup
and disaster recovery plans to handle major business interruptions.
Regular
maintenance and updating of computer systems to prevent unauthorised access.
When information is no longer required we ensure that it is deleted from our systems,
destroyed in a secure manner, or permanently de-identified.
Abby Eagle School of Meditation may be required by law to retain personal information
for a period of time after you have ceased your relationship with us. After the
required time has passed we attend to the secure destruction or deletion of personal
information.
OPENNESS
The Abby Eagle School of
Meditation Privacy Policy set out in this document can be viewed on our website.
On request from you, Abby Eagle School of Meditation will take reasonable steps
to let you know, generally, what sort of personal information it holds, for what
purposes, and how it collects, holds, uses and discloses that information.
ACCESS
AND CORRECTION
You
may request access to your personal information by contacting us at the address
at the end of this document Abby Eagle School of Meditation will endeavour to
handle all requests for personal information within 30 days of having received
the request. Some requests may take longer than 30 days, depending on the information
sought, in which case you will be notified of the expected time frame as soon
as is practicable. In some situations, where the information requested goes beyond
a basic summary, a fee may be charged for access. This fee is used to cover the
cost to Abby Eagle School of Meditation for retrieving and supplying the information.
If you are able to establish that the information we hold about you is not accurate,
complete and up-to-date, Abby Eagle School of Meditation will take reasonable
steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
You may have access to your
personal information, except to the extent that:
Providing
access would pose a serious and imminent threat to the life or health of any individual;
or
Providing
access would have an unreasonable impact upon the privacy of other individuals;
or
The request
is frivolous or vexatious; or
The
information relates to existing or anticipated legal proceedings between Rejoice-In-Life
and yourself, and the information would not be accessible by the process of discovery
in those proceedings; or
Providing
access would reveal the intentions of the Rejoice-In-Life in relation to negotiations
with you in such a way as to prejudice those negotiations; or
Providing
access would be likely to prejudice an investigation of possible unlawful activity;
or
providing
access would be likely to prejudice: the prevention, detection, investigation,
prosecution or punishment of criminal offences, breaches of a law imposing a penalty
or sanction or breaches of a prescribed law; or the enforcement of laws relating
to the confiscation of the proceeds of crime; or the protection of the public
revenue; or the prevention, detection, investigation or remedying of seriously
improper conduct or prescribed conduct; or the preparation for, or conduct of,
proceedings before any court or tribunal, or implementation of its orders; by
or on behalf of an enforcement body; or an enforcement body performing a lawful
security function asks Rejoice-In-Life not to provide access to the information
on the basis that providing access would be likely to cause damage to the security
of Australia.
However,
where providing access would reveal evaluative information generated within Abby Eagle School of Meditation in connection with a commercially sensitive decision-making
process, Abby Eagle School of Meditation may give the individual an explanation
for the commercially sensitive decision rather than direct access to the information.
If the organisation is not
required to provide the individual with access to the information Abby Eagle
School of Meditation may, if reasonable, consider whether the use of mutually
agreed intermediaries would allow sufficient access to meet the needs of both
parties.
IDENTIFIERS
Abby Eagle School of Meditation
does not collect or use Commonwealth identifiers. In managing its database, Rejoice-In-Life
may use a number assigned by us, to you, to uniquely identify you for the purposes
of carrying on our operations.
ANONYMITY
Wherever it is lawful and practicable
to do so Abby Eagle School of Meditation will endeavour to deal with you anonymously,
however in most cases it is not possible to do business with you unless we have
appropriate identification.
TRANS
BORDER DATA FLOWS
Abby Eagle School of Meditation does not transfer personal information about you
to anyone outside of Australia unless we are authorised to do so, as in the nature
of carrying on our normal business activities, or required to by law. Abby Eagle
School of Meditation will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information
which it has transferred will not be held, used or disclosed by the recipient
of the information inconsistently with the National Privacy Principles.
INTERNET
Generally email is not a secure
way to communicate therefor you should not send us personal information to us
via email.
About Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:
The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this web site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of this site based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Data collection of non-personally identifying information:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Linking to other sites.
Our website contains links to other sites. We, Abby Eagle School of Meditation are not
responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We
encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy
statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable
information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by
this website.
Online payments.
We use a third party credit card processor so we do not
store sensitive financial information. The credit card processor provides
information to the site about whether the charge transaction was approved or
not.
OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
We never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.
UPDATING
THIS PRIVACY POLICY
Abby Eagle School of Meditation attempts to keep all its policies and procedures
up to date with changes in the law, technology and market practice. As
a result we may change this privacy policy from time to time. This policy was
last amended on 16th May 2010.
COMPLAINTS
Any complaints with regard
to the handling of your personal information in breach of this Privacy Policy
should be directed to:
Any complaints that have not been handled satisfactorily by Abby Eagle can be
referred to the Federal Privacy Commissioner:
Send a message and we'll get back to you asap.
CONGO,
ISLANDS (MALVINAS)
SEE (VATICAN CITY STATE)
IRAN,
KOREA,
DEMOCRATIC PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC OF
KOREA,
MACEDONIA,
MICRONESIA,
TANZANIA,
ISLANDS, U.S.
...
